Isn't it really cute?
めっちゃかわいいじゃないですか
It's so cute.
め っちゃかわいい
Like that, like that.
そうやって、そうやって
Isn't it really cute?
めっちゃかわいいじゃないですか
How old are you?
おいくつですか?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
18歳ね
Today is
今日は、
I eat a lot.
い っぱいするんですけど
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
Is it okay?
いいの?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみです
Are you looking forward to it?
楽しみなの?
When an 18-year-old asks me to look forward to it,
18歳に楽しみなって言われたら、
It makes me nervous.
緊張するね
turn slowly
ゆっくり回って
Let's see.
み よう
I can feel it.
感じちゃいます
Are you wearing a bra?
ブラつけてるでしょ?
What do you usually eat?
普段、おなにするの?
normally?
普段?
What are you going to do?
おなにする?
I won't do anything to you.
おなにはしない
I won't.
しないね
So, sit there again.
じゃあ、そこでもう一回座って
that
それを
...
I feel it.
感じ ます
feel?
感じる?
It's my first time.
初めてなんだ
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
It's a skirt.
スカートなんだ
I thought it was pants.
ズボンかと思った
Let's move on a little further.
もうちょっと前を置いて
Leave it here.
ここまで置いて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I make it stronger?
もっと強くしていい?
This is no good.
これはダメです
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
This feels so good.
これが気持ちよすぎます
Wait, can I go?
ちょっと、行っていいんだろう?
Maybe I can go.
行けるかも
I can go.
行けるね
Are you going?
行くの?
I went.
行っちゃった
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
I went.
行っちゃった
On your back.
背中をつけて
Raise your legs up.
足を上に上げて
Once again, show me exactly where you're going.
もう一回、行くとこちゃんと見せて
Look at this guy.
こいつ見て
I'll go right away.
すぐ行っちゃうじゃん
No more.
もうダメ
I'll go right away.
すぐ行っちゃうじゃん
thin.
細い
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
All I wanted to do was sleep.
全部寝たくて
What should I do?
どうしよう
Look around.
回ってごらん
細
stomach.
い
It's thin.
細 いよ
No.
ダメ
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
Are you going to quit?
やめちゃう?
No.
ダメ
It's beautiful.
綺麗じゃん
No way.
ダメだもん
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
I want to do it quickly.
早くしたいよね
Should I hurry?
早くしよっか
It's a soft-shelled turtle.
すっぽんぽんじゃん
You don't have to show it.
見せなくていいね
What should I do?
どうしよう
It's kind of difficult.
なんか難しい
Is it hard?
つらいの?
You're being touched.
おまえが触られてる
What are you doing?
何をされてるの?
You're being touched.
おまえが触られてる
It's really wet.
うまくびっちょびっちょだよ
Look!
見てごらん
I'm sure my neck is getting better too.
首もきっとなってる
I can't use anything.
何も使えない
Push harder.
もっと押して
It's no good if you don't look properly when you go.
行くときちゃんと見なくてダメだよ
Even if you make it look good.
ちゃんと見えるようにしても
Stretch out your sweat.
汗伸ばして
It's about to get a lot bigger.
これからすごく大きくなってる
copper
どう
Will it become?
なる の?
What will happen?
どうなるの?
I have to look at it properly.
ちゃんと見なくては
I saw it.
見ちゃった
Back and forth.
前後に
Before and after?
前後に?
It's too closed.
閉まりすぎなんだよ
It doesn't fit at all.
全然入らない
It's soaking wet.
びっちょびっちょだよ
My bottom is jumpy.
びくびくしてる下が
Even though it's wet, it's small.
びっちょびっちょなのに小さいよ
I can't get it out at all.
全然抜けない
It doesn't come off at all.
全然抜けないし
This is really tight.
すごい締まりだよ、これ
It's amazingly absorbing.
すごい 吸い付いてる
It sucks me so much.
こんなに吸い付いて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I feel like I'm getting screwed.
なんかズボズボされてる
Did you see it?
見ちゃったの?
It won't come off at all.
全然抜けないよ
Pull it out yourself.
自分で抜いてほら
Squeak.
キュッキュって
Just my pussy.
おまんこだけで
That's amazing.
すごいね
Look here.
こっち見て
cute.
かわいい
It's cute.
かわいいね
Spread your legs.
足広がって
No?
だめなの?
it hurts.
痛い
It's cute.
かわいいね
Open your pussy and see.
おまんこ開いてほら
Open your pussy yourself.
自分でおまんこ開いてほら
Pussy.
おまんこ
That's naughty.
やらしい
Look here.
こっち見て
You don't have to show it at all.
全然見せなくていい
Touch Kure-chan yourself.
自分でくれちゃん触ってほら
You don't have to show it at all.
全然見せなくていい
Go ahead and call me.
電話で行ってほら
It's a pussy.
おまんこだね
Small.
ちっちゃい
Shall we go?
行っちゃう?
go.
行く
hang on.
待って
good?
いい?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Lick from above?
上から舐める?
yes.
そう
Touch from above.
上から触る
From above the pants.
パンツの上から
This is it.
これね
mosquito
か
Okay.
わ いい
Soaked.
びちょびちょ
It's soaking wet.
びちょびちょじゃん
Look.
ほ ら
Just keep licking it.
どんどん舐めてほら
If you lick me that much.
そんなに舐めたら
Take it all off.
全部脱がして
To the depths.
その奥まで
I'm doing something very naughty.
すごいエッチなままやことしてる
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
Look here.
こっち見て
amazing.
すごい
I'm putting it in my pussy.
おまんこ入れてる
Are you going to lick that deep?
そんな奥まで舐めるの?
I'm starting to want to include it.
入れたくなってきた
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I entered.
入った
To the back.
奥まで
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
It's really intense.
すごい激しいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
beautiful.
きれい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Ah, I've reached my limit.
あ、もう限界
It's already the limit.
もう限界
Get your hands behind me.
後ろに手ついて
Your pussy is so wet.
おまんこびちょびちょじゃん
Because it feels good.
気持ちいいから
a,
あ、
No, no, no.
ダ メダメダメ
It feels amazing though.
すーごい気持ちいいんだけど
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What's going on?
どう なってる?
It's in.
入ってる
Your pussy is small.
おまんこ小さいよ
amazing.
すごい
Holding back?
後ろ持ち?
Hold back.
後ろ持ち
Leave it in?
入れたまま?
That's right.
そうだよ
You're doing a great job.
すごい手ついてる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's not easy to move forward.
もう少し前へとは楽じゃない
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいいよ
It's really absorbing.
めっちゃ吸い付いてる
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎる
No, no, no.
ダメダメダメ
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり
Great go.
すごい行く
No, go.
ダ メ行く
I'll go.
行くよ
Go, go, go.
行 く行く
It's too cute.
可愛すぎるよ
Just keep your legs open.
そのまま足開いてて
It's out.
出てる
Look.
見て
Look, look.
見て 見て
You can cue.
キューってできる
Because it's small.
小さいから
Is it because it's small?
小さいから?
It won't come out.
出てこないよ
I spent a lot of money on it.
相当出したもん
It doesn't come out.
出 てこない
I'm trying my best though.
頑張ってるけど
It doesn't come out at all.
全然出てこない
It came out.
出た
Good luck and good luck.
頑張って頑張って
I'll put my finger in there a little bit.
少し指入れるよ
It's small.
小さいんですよ
Try removing it.
手外してみて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I let it go too far inside.
奥に出しすぎちゃった
Shall I just wake up for a little while?
そのまま少し起きてみようか
Just a little bit.
少しだけ
With this.
これで
I can make it squeak.
キュッキュッってできる
It doesn't come out.
出てこない
出 てこない
I took it really deep inside.
めっちゃ奥に出しちゃった
What should I do?
どうする?
It's no good if you stay calm.
冷静にしたらダメ
Is it okay if I stay calm?
冷静にしたらダメなの?
No.
ダメ
Thank you for today.
今日はありがとね
Wait, I'll take a picture.
待って、撮ってくれます